there may be occasions where you've been
working on a document and you saved it
into a folder and there may be
confidential information in there or
information that you don't want anybody
else to see to avoid that you can see if
the document with the password so that
only those with access to the password
are able to open the document so for
example I have a file here that I
created earlier called password which I
will order and as it says just a
demonstration document but I want to
make sure that nobody without the
password can open that file so they're
gonna fail
and then 2 in 4 I can click on protect
document and trip with password and
create a password for the file it will
ask you to enter it twice just to make
sure that everything is correct once
I've done that that is now protected so
if I close that document I click see if
and then go back to my folder and open
the document again it will automatically
ask me for a password once it's entered
they will open the document if you just
say to delete a deer that you wish to
remove the password all youtubers would
fail in 4 click on protect document
encrypt with password and take the
password out thank you
that then means that it is now able to
be opened by anyone alternatively it may
be a kiss that you want the document
just to be read only absorb people can
read the document put the card make any
changes to it to do that if you have to
develop a table on your computer you can
click on that a hands up doesn't icon
called restrict editing if you click on
the restrict editing button it will
allow you to set it so that the only
restrictions is that people can read the
document they are not allowed to make
any changes so once that's applied and
you've clicked the bottom button which
is yes start enforcing protection
again it will ask you for a password so
I'll take the password in man and fill
the password here so again if I save
that and close it and then open it again
now while it hasn't got a password on to
Orban I cannot make any changes so it
actually gives you the warning this
document is protected from unintentional
heading you need to only view in this
region they took stop protection without
the password it would be unable to edit
the document